Yule believe in miracles.
Once Upon a Deadpool is a comedy, action,
adventure film directed by David Leitch.
A kidnapped Fred Savage is forced to endure Deadpool's PG-13 rendition of Deadpool 2, as
a Princess Bride-esque story that's full of magic, wonder, and zero Fs.
Wade Wilson / Deadpool / Juggernaut (voice), played by Ryan Reynolds.
Cable, played by Josh Brolin.
Vanessa, played by Morena Baccarin.
Firefist, played by Julian Dennison.
Domino, played by Zazie Beetz.
Weasel, played by T.J. Miller.
Deadpool 2 is a 2018 American  superhero film based on
the Marvel Comics character Deadpool.
It is the sequel to Deadpool (2016) and the eleventh
installment in the X-Men film series.
The film was directed by David Leitch and written by Rhett Reese, Paul Wernick, and Ryan Reynolds, who stars
in the title role alongside Josh Brolin, Morena Baccarin, Julian Dennison, Zazie Beetz, T.J.
Miller, Brianna Hildebrand, and Jack Kesy.
In the film, Deadpool forms the X-Force to protect a young
mutant from the time-traveling soldier Cable.
Plans for a sequel to Deadpool began before the original film's
release, and were confirmed in February 2016.
Though the original creative team of Reynolds, Reese, Wernick, and director Tim Miller were set to return for the second film,
Miller left the project in October 2016 due to creative differences with Reynolds and was soon replaced by Leitch.
An extensive casting search took place to fill the role
of Cable, with Brolin ultimately cast.
Principal photography took place in British Columbia from June to October 2017.
Deadpool 2 premiered at the Empire Leicester Square in London on May 10, 2018, and
was released in the United States on May 18, by 20th Century Fox.
The film outgrossed its predecessor, earning $785.9 million worldwide against a $110 million production budget, becoming the ninth
highest-grossing film of 2018, the highest-grossing film in the X-Men series, and the highest-grossing R-rated film at the time of its release.
The film received positive reviews from critics, with some considering it superior to the first film and praising its humor,
cast performances, story, and action sequences, while others criticized its tone, script, and recycled jokes.
A PG-13-rated version of the film, titled Once Upon a Deadpool, was
released on December 12, 2018, to mixed reviews.
Following the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by Disney,
Deadpool's film rights were returned to Marvel Studios.
A sequel, Deadpool & Wolverine, starring Reynolds and Hugh Jackman and integrating their characters into the
Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU), was released on July 26, 2024, as part of Phase Five of the MCU.
The film explores themes of superhero, based on comic, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.